Tony Truong

Seasoned Pharmacy Technician with 14+ years of experience in data entry, pharmaceutical knowledge, passion individual, adaptable, with knowledge of medical records computing. Knowledge of electronic medical records programs. Proficient in prescription processing, prescription filling with many different types of packaging. Maintain a healthy relationship with accounts and nurses.

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ tonyltruong/ (425) 381-1323 ttruong1989@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Mercury Pharmacy Services, Mountlake Terrace, WA — *Account Manager*

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT

- Maintain a healthy relationship with nurses to ensure a good communication between the pharmacy and retirement facility.
- Be the point of contact for any concerns or questions that arose.
 Ensure that all requirements for each account are met and all medications are handled properly and that everything meets the Washington State Board standard and company policies.
- Provided a monthly report on residents medications and communicated with the nurses on which one is discontinued and add any missing new medications.
- Provide training for new employees to ensure they fully understand the systems and how to fix common errors.
- Daily to Weekly follow up with nurses to ensure there aren't any new requirements or demands. Address all concerns or questions.
- Provide assistance to nurses with electronic medical records systems and provide live support for troubleshooting QuickMAR.

Mercury Pharmacy Services, Mountlake Terrace, WA — Data Entry/Pharmacy Technician

MARCH 2014 - JUNE 2018

- Provide help to the pharmacist with prescription entering,
- Helping pharmacy assistants with medication related questions.
- Also performed refill phone calls to the doctor's office to obtain refill authorization and perform the required refills.

Mercury Pharmacy Services, Mountlake Terrace, WA — *Pharmacy Assistant*

JUNE 2008 - MARCH 2014

- Packaging medications label.
- Help run and maintain the medications filling robot.

EDUCATION

University of Phoenix, September 2022 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

SKILLS

Working knowledge of SQL, Python, JavaScript, C#, C++

Microsoft Office

Google Workspace

Proficient with computers, handheld devices, computer software, medical software

Hands on learner

Communication

Problem Solver

CERTIFICATION

Advanced Software Developer Certificate (Univ. of Phoenix)

Washington State Pharmacy Technician Licenses

LANGUAGES

English, Vietnamese